<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Motorola services</string>
    <string name="cloudpicker_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="permlab_interactBlurService">Interact with the Blur service</string>
    <string name="permdesc_interactBlurService">Needed if you want to talk to the Blur service. If missing, no communication with remote service will be possible and stuff won\'t work.</string>
    <string name="permlab_emailActionSend">Send an email via the Blur Email Service.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_emailActionSend">Needed if you want to send an email via an Intent broadcast using the Blur Email Service. If missing, an email cannot be sent.</string>
    <string name="permlab_snmessagingActionSend">Send a social message via the Blur Service.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_snmessagingActionSend">Needed if you want to send a social message via an Intent broadcast using the Blur Service. If missing, a social message cannot be sent.</string>
    <string name="permlab_snmessagingInteract">Access Blur Email Service data and components.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_snmessagingInteract">Needed to interact with the Blur Email Service. If missing, no Social messaging database access is allowed, no Social messaging Intents will be received and no Social messaging sync requests allowed.</string>
    <string name="permlab_emailInteract">Access Blur Email Service data and components.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_emailInteract">Needed to interact with the Blur Email Service. If missing, no Email Service database access is allowed, no Email Service Intents will be received and no Email Service sync requests allowed.</string>
    <string name="permlab_emailEngine">Blur Email Engine component.</string>
    <string name="permdesc_emailEngine">Permission used internally by components of the Blur Email Service.</string>
    <string name="label_access_accounts">Access accounts</string>
    <string name="desc_access_accounts">Needed for an application to access account information stored in the Accounts Preference Panel</string>
    <string name="wipe_device_perm_desc">Allows application to request that the device be wiped.</string>
    <string name="wipe_device_perm_label">Allowed to request the device be wiped</string>
    <string name="permlab_read_data">Read social networking data</string>
    <string name="permdesc_read_data">Allows the application to read any social networking data. Malicious applications may read personal information.</string>
    <string name="permlab_write_data">Write social networking data</string>
    <string name="permdesc_write_data">Allows the application to write to the social networking database. Malicious applications may corrupt data presented to you.</string>
    <string name="permlab_use_social_networks">Use social networking features</string>
    <string name="permdesc_use_social_networks">Allows the application to use features of a social networking provider. Malicious applications may manipulate your personal information on a social network.</string>
    <string name="permlab_social_contact_read">Read social networking contacts</string>
    <string name="permdesc_social_contact_read">Needed if you want to read social networking contacts. If missing you cannot read social networking contacts.</string>
    <string name="permlab_social_contact_write">Write social networking contacts</string>
    <string name="permdesc_social_contact_write">Needed if you want to write social networking contacts. If missing you cannot write or modify social networking contacts.</string>
    <string name="permlab_suggestions_schedule">Schedule suggestion rule check services</string>
    <string name="permdesc_suggestions_schedule">Needed if you want to schedule a service to check suggestion rules.</string>
    <string name="permlab_suggestions_read">Read contacts and groups suggestions</string>
    <string name="permdesc_suggestions_read">Needed if you want to read contacts and groups suggestions.</string>
    <string name="permlab_suggestions_write">Write contacts and groups suggestions</string>
    <string name="permdesc_suggestions_write">Needed if you want to write data for contacts or groups suggestions.</string>
    <string name="permlab_datacollector_read">Read general collected data</string>
    <string name="permdesc_datacollector_read">Needed if you want to read general collected user communication data.</string>
    <string name="permlab_datacollector_write">Write general collected data</string>
    <string name="permdesc_datacollector_write">Needed if you want to write general collected user communication data.</string>
    <string name="permlab_imps_srv">Start IM service</string>
    <string name="permdesc_imps_srv">Allows applications to start IM service via an intent.</string>
    <string name="permlab_imps_ro">Read instant messages</string>
    <string name="permdesc_imps_ro">Allows applications to read data from the IM content provider\".</string>
    <string name="permlab_imps_wo">Write instant messages</string>
    <string name="permdesc_imps_wo">Allows applications to write data to the IM content provider\".</string>
    <string name="gams_accountName">Motorola</string>
</resources>